>> Brian Holt: 欢迎使用 Intermediate React V2。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Welcome to
the Intermediate React V2.
我很高兴能在这里跟你谈谈雷法的事
I'm really excited to be here
talking to you about React again.
今天我们要讨论的是延伸的 " 雷法 " 生态系统。
And today we're gonna be talking
about the extended React ecosystem.
>> Brian Holt: 正在重新执行
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: React in and
本身并不是通常用于构建项目的唯一工具。
of itself is not typically the only
tool that you use to build a project.
你会把像E原动议一样的东西带进来
You're gonna bring in things like
Emotion to do CSS, you're gonna do Node
服务器端呈现，您要执行代码分割，以及所有这些内容。
server-side rendering, you're gonna do
code splitting, and all that kinda stuff.
所以中间 React 的目的就是要教你
And so that's what intermediate
React aims to teach you,
是这种扩展的生态系统类型
is these kind of extended
ecosystem type of things.
所以我要你做的第一件事就是去 bit.ly， B-I-T-L-Y。
So the first thing I want you to
do is go to bit.ly, B-I-T-L-Y.
请使用 Bit.ly，而不是 /reat-v5。
Bit.ly, rather, /react-v5.
这应该带你到这个网站
And that should take you
to this website here.
你也可以把这两个工作都联系起来。
You can also just go to this link
up there as well, those both work.
这是我的课程笔记是吧
These are my course notes, right?
你看到我在这儿有个表面
So you see that I have a Surface here.
其实我在你面前所看到的，也是我在这里所看到的。
Literally what I have on what you see in
front of you is what I have here as well.
所以如果你迷路了什么的
So If you get lost or anything like that,
你就能自由地跳进我的笔记里然后再看一下
you can feel free to just jump into my
notes and take a look at that as well.
所以关于这个网站要注意的事是完整的 " 再行动" 的简介
So, the thing to note about this website
is both the complete the intro to React,
简介部分在这里，中间部分是。
the intro part is in here,
and the intermediate part is.
因此，引入部分在此处是 1 到 15 。
So, the introduction part
is 1 through 15 here.
因此，结束后的一切都是这一过程的中间部分。
So everything after conclusion is
the intermediate part of this course.
知道这件事的是我们仍在用同样的项目
The thing to know about this is that
we're still gonna use the same project
从这个课程的第一个版本开始，我们将会增加这个项目。
from the first version of this course,
and we're just going to augment that.
现在你不用做引言了
Now, you don't have to have
taken the introduction,
你要是有就很有帮助但你不用做介绍
it's helpful if you have, but you don't
have to have taken the introduction
来完成这部分课程
to do this part of the course.
另一件值得注意的是与引言相反
The other thing to note,
as opposed to the introduction,
每一个都是一个分支，对吧 ?
is each one of these is a branch, right?
所以每一个都是完全被筛选的。
So each one of these is totally siloed.
所以如果你想跳过E动议，直接去做代码分割，你可以。
So if you wanna skip Emotion and
go straight to Code Splitting, you can.
所以每一个都在一个不同的仓里。
So each one of these is
totally in a different silo.
作为引言，你可以看到我在这里所拥有的一切。
As by way of introduction,
you can read everything that I have here.
但只要说我是谁我叫布莱恩 - 霍尔特
But just to say who I am,
my name's Brian Holt.
我在微软工作
I work at Microsoft.
我以前是个云代言人现在我是高级计划经理
I used to be a cloud advocate, and
now I'm a senior program manager
在 Azure 上的 Node.js 以及 Visual Studio 代码。
on Node.js on Azure,
as well as on Visual Studio Code.
我住在西雅图和我的妻子和我的狗
I live in Seattle with my wife and my dog.
我有时在欢乐的时候在前面说话
And I sometimes talk out
in front in happy hour.
我是一个董事会成员
I am a board member for
Vet Who Code 以及非洲会议的共同创始人， Concatenate公司。
Vet Who Code as well as a co-founder
of the African conference, Concatenate.
在这里的社交媒体上，我可以自由地与我联系，我也有我的所有联系。
Feel free to catch up with me on social
media here, I have all my links as well.
我一直都是在前线老师教这些东西
And I'm stoked as always to be here at
Frontend Masters teaching the stuff
我很喜欢教书
that I love to teach.
我真的很高兴他们鼓励我打开我的材料
And I'm really, really happy that they
encouraged me to open source my materials
这样你就能和同事一起分享这些了
so that you can share these with
your coworkers, and with anyone.
像往常一样，如果你把雷波放在 GitHub 上，这对我很有帮助。
As always, it's really helpful for
me if you star the repo on GitHub so
其他人也能找到这个
that other people can find this as well.
太酷了
Cool.
所以在这里的引言中
So inside of this introduction here,
在上面写着长串的数字和字母
underneath where it says long
series of numbers and letters.
如果您单击此存储库，那么会将您转至 GitHub 存储库
If you click on the repo is here,
this'll take you to the GitHub repo for
这门课
this course.
所以你在这里看到的是完成的
So what you see here in
the masterbranch is the finished
React 项目的完整简介，好吗 ?
a Complete Intro to React project, okay?
这就是它在完成  之后的状态。
So this is the state that it's in after
you do the Complete Intro to React.
我们要做的是我们要做的是
What we're going to do for every single
section of this particular course is we're
然后再回到主子里然后我们又要重新开始了对吧
gonna go back to the master branch, and
then we're going to start again, right?
一旦我们完成了E议案，我们就会回到主子部门，
So as soon as we finish Emotion, we're
going to go back to the master branch, and
然后我们就开始做服务器端渲染或者类似的事情
then we're gonna start on server side
rendering or something like that.
只要你对任何事情都做了就把你的所有属地都清楚
So as soon as you're done with any
section, just clear all your dependencies,
除去节点模块，运行 npm 安装。
remove your node modules, run npm install.
我要提醒你我们正在进行的事情。
And I'll remind you of these
things as we're going along.
或者您可以克隆新版本的存储库或
Or you can just clone a new
version of the repo or
你可以打开一个新的分支，这些都是不错的事情。
you can open a new branch,
those are all fine things to do.
但是如果你想看，我在这里就有了全部的工作。
But if you want to see,
I have all of the complete work up here.
如果您单击此信息，您可以看到代码分割。
If you click on this,
you can see that there's code splitting.
有E议案。
There's Emotion.
这两个用于 GitHub 页面，这是课程 Web站点。
These two are for the GitHub Pages,
which is the course website.
还有 Redux， SSR，测试和 TypeScript。
And then there's Redux, SSR,
testing, and TypeScript.
这些都在这里
Those are all here as well.
但是，对于每个新部分，您只需返回到干净的主分支。
But again, for each new section,
you just go back to a clean master branch.
你可以考虑使用 Sourcetree之类的东西
You might consider using
something like Sourcetree,
网址是sourcetreeapp.com 。
which you can get at sourcetreeapp.com.
如果你不太熟悉它就能帮你了
And this will help you if you're
not super familiar with git.
您还可以使用 GitHub Desktop。
You can also use GitHub Desktop.
我只是用命令行
I just use the command line.
所以你可以自由地使用最适合你的东西
So feel free to use
whatever suits you best.
但我建议你把它叫做 " 深度 Git "
But I would suggest you take
's course called Git in Depth.
Git 绝对是一个值得了解的工具。
Git is definitely a tool
that's worth knowing.